<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sandpiper Cookbook</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/</link><description>Recent content on Sandpiper Cookbook</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:51:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Title for your recipe</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sample/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 14:51:17 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sample/</guid><description>Ingredients Ingredient Subheading First Ingredient Second Ingredient 1 Third Ingredient Fourth Ingredient Fifth Ingredient Directions Step One Sub Step One Step Two Step Three Step Four Step Five Step Six Footnotes Footnote 1&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Baked French Toast</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/baked.french.toast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/baked.french.toast/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 4 hours
Ingredients some Butter 1 loaf Italian bread, sliced 1 cup brown sugar 1 tsp cinnamon 6 eggs 1.5 cups milk some nuts 1 can pie filling (your choice) 1 tsp vanilla Cookware 13x9 baking dish oven Steps Butter a 13x9 baking dish. [Butter: some] Spread pie filling (your choice) on the bottom of the dish. [pie filling (your choice): 1 can] Sprinkle on cinnamon and nuts (optional), and brown sugar.</description></item><item><title>Beef And Broccoli</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/beef.and.broccoli/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/beef.and.broccoli/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 20 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 8 ounces beef tenderloin 8 ounces broccoli florets 2 tsp minced garlic some oil 2 tbsp oyster sauce 1 pack pad thai rice noodles 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp sugar Cookware skillet Steps Soak the pad thai rice noodles in hot water for 10 minutes or until tender. Drain and rinse under cold water and set aside.</description></item><item><title>Beer Cheese</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/beer.cheese/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/beer.cheese/</guid><description>Facts Source: Emma; Total Time: 25 minutes
Ingredients 0.75 cups beer 1 pound cheddar cheese 1 tbsp flour 1 clove garlic 1 dash ground cayenne 1.5 tsp ground mustard 2 tbsp worcestershire sauce Cookware fondue pot bowl Steps Peel the garlic and cut in half. Rub the cut sides over inside surface of the fondue pot. [garlic: 1 clove] In a bowl, combine the cheddar cheese, flour, ground mustard and ground cayenne; mix to blend thoroughly.</description></item><item><title>Bite Steaks</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/bite.steaks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/bite.steaks/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1.5 hours; Source: Aunt Julie
Ingredients 1 can beef broth 1 can french onion soup 2 tsp garlic 2 tbsp oil 0.5 onion some pepper 1.5 pounds round eye steak some salt Steps Brown the onion, garlic and round eye steak in oil, cut into bite sized pieces until brown and the onions are tender. [garlic: 2 tsp; oil: 2 tbsp; onion: 0.5; round eye steak: 1.</description></item><item><title>Black Bean Pie</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/black.bean.pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/black.bean.pie/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 1 hour
Ingredients 2 cans black beans 1.5 cups chicken stock 0.5 tsp cumin 8 ounces frozen corn 1 jalapeno some minced garlic 1 tbsp oil 1 onion some pam some pepper some salt some scallions some shredded cheddar 3 tortillas Cookware skillet Steps Spray both sides of tortillas with pam and fry until golden brown in a skillet on each side.</description></item><item><title>Black Bean Salad</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/black.bean.salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/black.bean.salad/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 20 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 cans black beans 1 tsp black pepper 15 ounces canned corn 1 tbsp cilantro 0.25 cups diced green onion 0.25 cups diced pineapple 0.25 cups diced red bell pepper 0.25 cups diced red onion 2 diced roma tomato 3 tbsp honey 1 jalapeno 1 tbsp salt 4 tbsp sherry vinegar Steps Mix the drained and rinsed black beans, canned corn, diced roma tomato, diced red bell pepper, diced red onion, diced green onion, diced pineapple, cilantro, jalapeno (seeded and diced), sherry vinegar, honey, salt, black pepper and refrigare for one hour.</description></item><item><title>Blueberry Compote</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/blueberry.compote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/blueberry.compote/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 20 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 cups fresh blueberries 1 cup sugar 1 cup water Cookware pot Steps Add fresh blueberries, water and sugar to a pot and cook over medium heat for about 20 minutes, until it is thick like jam. [fresh blueberries: 2 cups; sugar: 1 cup; water: 1 cup]</description></item><item><title>Broccoli Alfredo</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/broccoli.alfredo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/broccoli.alfredo/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 45 minutes
Ingredients 4 tbsp butter 4 cups chicken stock 1 head chopped broccoli 1 cup heavy cream 2 tbsp minced garlic 1 tbsp olive oil 0.75 cups parmesan 1 pound penne pasta 0.25 tsp pepper 1 tsp salt Cookware large skillet Steps Add penne pasta, minced garlic, salt, pepper, olive oil and chicken stock to a large skillet. [chicken stock: 4 cups; minced garlic: 2 tbsp; olive oil: 1 tbsp; penne pasta: 1 pound; pepper: 0.</description></item><item><title>Broccoli Ham Ring</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/broccoli.ham.ring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/broccoli.ham.ring/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 45 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2.2 cups chopped broccoli 2 tubes crescent dough 0.25 cups diced ham 2 tbsp dijon mustard 1 tsp lemon juice 0.5 onion 1.5 cups shredded swiss cheese Cookware round baking pan pizza sheet large bowl Steps Unroll crescent dough and place triangles over a round baking pan or pizza sheet. [crescent dough: 2 tubes] In a large bowl combine shredded swiss cheese, chopped broccoli, diced ham, onion, dijon mustard and lemon juice.</description></item><item><title>Buffalo Chicken Dip</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/buffalo.chicken.dip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/buffalo.chicken.dip/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 20 minutes
Ingredients 1.5 cups cheddar cheese 20 ounces chuck ckicken some crackers 16 ounces cream cheese 0.75 cups hot sauce some pretzels 1 cup ranch Cookware medium pot Steps Heat chuck ckicken (drained), cream cheese, ranch, hot sauce, cheddar cheese in a medium pot and stir until warm and melted. [cheddar cheese: 1.5 cups; chuck ckicken: 20 ounces; cream cheese: 16 ounces; hot sauce: 0.</description></item><item><title>Cabbage Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cabbage.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cabbage.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 tsp apple cider vinegar 1 bay leaf 32 ounces beef broth 2 tbsp brown sugar 1 can diced tomato 2 tbsp fresh parsley 2 cloves garlic 1 pound green cabbage 1 pound ground beef 2 medium carrots 1 medium onion 1 tbsp olive oil 1.5 tsp paprika 0.25 tsp pepper 1 tsp salt 1 cup water 0.5 cups white rice 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce Cookware bowl bowl large pot dutch oven wooden spoon Steps Dice medium onion, mince garlic and place both in the same bowl.</description></item><item><title>Caramel Snack</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/caramel.snack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/caramel.snack/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1.5 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 cup brown sugar 0.5 cups butter 12 ounces chex cereal 0.75 cups corn syrup 1 cup nuts some pam Cookware oven mircowave safe bowl Steps Preheat oven to 275 Spary large raosting pan with pam. [pam: some] In a mircowave safe bowl, mix butter, corn syrup and brown sugar. [brown sugar: 1 cup; butter: 0.5 cups; corn syrup: 0.</description></item><item><title>Cheddar Biscuits</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cheddar.biscuits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cheddar.biscuits/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 20 minutes; Source: Red Lobster
Ingredients 2 cups bisquik 2 tbsp butter 1 cup cheddar cheese 0.5 tsp garlic powder 0.67 cups milk 2 tsp oregano some pam 0.25 tsp salt Cookware oven baking sheet parchment paper medium bowl Steps Preheat oven to 400 degrees. Line a baking sheet with parchment paper and spray with pam. [pam: some] Mix together the bisquik, cheddar cheese and garlic powder.</description></item><item><title>Cheesy Potatoes</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cheesy.potatoes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/cheesy.potatoes/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 1.5 hours
Ingredients 1 cup cream of chicken soup 36 ounces frozen hash browns 2 cups shredded cheese 1 cup soup cream Cookware 13x9 pan Steps Mix frozen hash browns, soup cream, cream of chicken soup and shredded cheese in a 13x9 pan at 350 degrees for 1 hour or until hot and bubbly. [cream of chicken soup: 1 cup; frozen hash browns: 36 ounces; shredded cheese: 2 cups; soup cream: 1 cup]</description></item><item><title>Chicken And Dumplings</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.and.dumplings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.and.dumplings/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1.5 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 4 tsp baking powder 4 tsp butter 6 chicken breasts 1.8 cups chicken stock 2 ribs chopped celery 1.5 cups chopped onion 3 diced carrots 1 egg 2.5 cups flour 0.5 cups heavy cream 1 cup milk some pam 1 tsp pepper some rosemary 3 tsp salt 0.5 tsp thyme Cookware large pot 1 cup measure ice cream scoop clear pie plate knife Steps Season chicken breasts with salt and pepper.</description></item><item><title>Chicken And Waffles</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.and.waffles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.and.waffles/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 1 hour
Ingredients some Bisquik some black pepper 1.5 cups buttermilk some cayenne pepper 5 chicken -6 boneless breasts- 0.5 cups cornmeal 1.5 cups flour 2 tbsp hot sauce some oil some old bay 1 tsp paprika some salt Cookware gallon ziplock bag shallow tupperware large skillet oven Steps Cut up chicken into about 4 peices each, sprinkle with salt and black pepper.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Bacon Ranch Panini</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.bacon.ranch.panini/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.bacon.ranch.panini/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 8 slices bacon 4 tbsp butter 4 slices cheddar cheese 4 chicken breasts 8 slices french bread 1 tbsp oil some pepper some ranch some salt some spicy mustard Steps Coat each side of the chicken breasts with salt and pepper. [chicken breasts: 4; pepper: some; salt: some] Fry the chicken in butter and oil for about 5 minutes on each side, until golden brown.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Ceasar Salad</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.ceasar.salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.ceasar.salad/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 4 chicken breast some croutons 1 lemon 1 tbsp minced garlic 0.5 cups olive oil some parmesan some pepper 4 romaine lettuce heats some salt Cookware grill grill pan serving bowl Steps Make a dressing by combining minced garlic, olive oil, salt, pepper and the juice from a lemon. Mix well, then set aside. [lemon: 1; minced garlic: 1 tbsp; olive oil: 0.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Enchiladas</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.enchiladas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.enchiladas/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1 hour; Source: Matt
Ingredients some cheddar cheese 4 chicken breast 2 tbsp chili powder some cilantro 2 tsp cumin 0.5 cups diced onion 4 ounces green chiles 1 tbsp minced garlic some oil some pam some pepper some salt 3 tsp suger 15 ounces tomato sauce 6 tortillas 1 cup water Cookware oven skillet cooking claws pan Steps Preheat oven to 400 degrees.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Flautas</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.flautas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.flautas/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients some avocado slices 2 cans cooked chicken some guacamole some oil some salsa some shredded cheddar cheese some tortilla Cookware medium bowl toothpicks frying pan Steps In a medium bowl mix cooked chicken, shredded cheddar cheese and salsa. [cooked chicken: 2 cans; salsa: some; shredded cheddar cheese: some] Scoop into tortilla and roll up, securing with toothpicks. [tortilla: some] Heat oil in frying pan and fry each tortilla until brown on each side.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Taco Salad</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.taco.salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.taco.salad/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 45 minutes
Ingredients 2 avocado 1 tbsp butter some cheddar cheese 4 chicken breast some fritos 10 ounces frozen corn 3 green onion 1 head lettuce some oil some ranch 2 roma tomato some salsa 1 pack taco seasoning Cookware frying pan salad bowl Steps Heat oil and butter in a frying pan. [butter: 1 tbsp; oil: some] Coat chicken breast with taco seasoning.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Torilla Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.torilla.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.torilla.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 8.5 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 15 ounces chicken stock 1 tsp chili powder 1 large can cooked chicken some crispy tortilla chips 1 tsp cumin 4 ounces diced green chili 10 ounces enchilda sauce 10 ounces frozen corn 2 tsp garlic 1 medium onion 0.25 tsp pepper 15 ounces petite diced tomatoes 1 tsp salt 2 cups water Cookware slow cooker Steps Place cooked chicken, petite diced tomatoes, enchilda sauce, medium onion, diced green chili and garlic into the slow cooker.</description></item><item><title>Chicken Tortellini Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.tortellini.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chicken.tortellini.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 4 hours; Source: Emma
Ingredients 9 ounces cheese tortellini 1 pound chicken breasts 6 cups chicken broth 1 diced onion 1 tsp minced garlic some parsley , 1 tsp- 0.5 tsp pepper 0.75 tsp salt 3 sliced carrots 0.5 tsp thyme Cookware slow cooker forks kitchen claws Steps Place the diced onion, sliced carrots, chicken breasts, minced garlic, salt, pepper, thyme, parsley and chicken broth into the slow cooker.</description></item><item><title>Chili</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chili/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chili/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 2 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 14 ounces black beans some cheddar cheese 2 tbsp chili powder 0.25 cups corn meal 1 tbsp cumin some fritos some green onions 2 pounds ground beef 14 ounces kindey beans 1 tbsp minced garlic 1 tsp oregano 10 ounces rotel 0.5 tsp salt 15 ounces tomato sauce 0.5 cups warm water Cookware medium pot Steps Brown ground beef with minced garlic over medium high heat in medium pot.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Eclair</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chocolate.eclair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chocolate.eclair/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 4 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 sleeves graham crackers 3 cups milk 6 ounces pudding mix 8 ounces thawed cool whip Cookware 13x9 pan large bowl mircowave Steps Line the bottom of a 13x9 pan with graham crackers. [graham crackers: 2 sleeves] In a large bowl, combine pudding mix and milk, stirring well. [milk: 3 cups; pudding mix: 6 ounces] Stir thawed cool whip into the pudding mixture, then spread half of the mixture over the graham crackers.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate Pie</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chocolate.pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/chocolate.pie/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 4 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 5 ounces chocolate pudding 3 cups milk 1 pie crust some whipped cream Steps Blind bake the pie crust at 450 degrees for 8 minutes. Cover the crust with 2 layers of tin foil. [pie crust: 1] After 8 minutes, remove foil and bake for another 6 minutes. Take out and let cool. Make the chocolate pudding with milk. Once cooled slightly (about 15 minutes) then pour into the pie crust and refrigate until eating.</description></item><item><title>Classic Taco Salad</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/classic.taco.salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/classic.taco.salad/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 14 ounces black beans some catalina dressing 12 ounces cheddar cheese some doritos 1 cup grape tomatoes 1 pound ground beef 1 head lettuce 1 package taco seasoning some water Cookware large bowl Steps Brown the ground beef and add taco seasoning and water. [ground beef: 1 pound; taco seasoning: 1 package; water: some] Place in a large bowl and add black beans, grape tomatoes (halved), lettuce (shredded), cheddar cheese, doritos.</description></item><item><title>Dumpling Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/dumpling.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/dumpling.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 45 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 6 cups chicken stock 2 cups cole saw mix 1.5 pounds frozen dumplings 0.5 bunches green onions 4 tsp minced garlic 1 tbsp olive oil 0.5 tsp salt 3 tbsp soy sauce 2 tbsp squeeze ginger Cookware large pot Steps Heat olive oil in a large pot over medium heat. [olive oil: 1 tbsp] Add minced garlic and squeeze ginger and saute for 3 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Fried Rice</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/fried.rice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/fried.rice/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 25 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 5 cups cold cooked rice 5 eggs 2 cups frozen vegetables 6 green onions 5 tbsp oil 2.5 tbsp oyster sauce some salt 1.5 tbsp soy sauce 1 tsp sugar 2 tsp white pepper Cookware bowl Steps In a bowl, whisk eggs with white pepper and season with salt. [eggs: 5; salt: some; white pepper: 1 tsp] Turn the heat up to medium-high and add in oil.</description></item><item><title>Grandma Schwennesen Potato Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/grandma.schwennesen.potato.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/grandma.schwennesen.potato.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1 hour; Source: Grandma Schwennesen
Ingredients 0.25 cups butter 6 cups chicken stock 3 chopped carrots 1 pound chopped kielbasa 2 cups milk 2 cups onion 4 potatoes Steps Saute onion and chopped carrots in butter until onion is tender. Add potatoes and chicken stock, then bring to a boil. [butter: 0.25 cups; chicken stock: 6 cups; chopped carrots: 3; onion: 2 cups; potatoes: 4] Reduce heat and simmer until vegatable are tender, approximatly 20 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Green Chile Enchiladas</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/green.chile.enchiladas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/green.chile.enchiladas/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 tbsp butter some cheddar cheese 1 large can cooked chicken 8 ounces green chiles 15 ounces green enchilada sauce 1 onion some salsa some tortilla Cookware small skillet small saucepan oven mircowave Steps In a small skillet, saute onion with butter over medium high heat until golden brown. [butter: 2 tbsp; onion: 1] In a small saucepan, combine green enchilada sauce with green chiles and heat until very warm.</description></item><item><title>Guacamole</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/guacamole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/guacamole/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 15 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 avocados some hot sauce some minced garlic some scallions some seasoned salt some tomatoes Cookware bowl Steps Mash the avocados in a bowl. [avocados: 2] Add minced garlic, seasoned salt and scallions. Can also add tomatoes or hot sauce if desired. [hot sauce: some; minced garlic: some; scallions: some; seasoned salt: some; tomatoes: some]</description></item><item><title>Ham And Swiss Rolls</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ham.and.swiss.rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ham.and.swiss.rolls/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 15 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 4 tbsp butter 1 tube crescent rolls some deli sliced ham 1 tbsp dijon mustard some poppy seeds 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce Steps Separate the crescent rolls into 8 triangles, then fold a piece of swiss cheese in half and place it in the center of the roll. [crescent rolls: 1 tube] Next, top it with some deli sliced ham.</description></item><item><title>Ham Cheese Sliders</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ham.cheese.sliders/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ham.cheese.sliders/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 tbsp butter 1 tbsp dijon mustard 1 tbsp flour 12 slices ham 12 hawaiian sweet rolls 1 cup milk some salt 6 slices swiss cheese Cookware oven small suacepan whisk Steps Preheat oven to 375 Slice hawaiian sweet rolls in half. [hawaiian sweet rolls: 12] Fold ham and swiss cheese and place them on the button bun.</description></item><item><title>Kartoffelpuffer</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/kartoffelpuffer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/kartoffelpuffer/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 30 minutes
Ingredients some applesauce 2 eggs 0.25 cups flour some fruit compote 1 grated onion 2.5 pounds grated potatoes 2 tbsp oil some powdered sugar 1 tsp salt Cookware colander dish towel medium-sized bowl non-stick pan spoon Steps Thoroughly wring out the liquid in the grated potatoes by placing them in a colander and seuqeezing them with your hands or placing them in a dish towel and wringing out the liquid.</description></item><item><title>Kluski Kładzione</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/kluski.k%C5%82adzione/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/kluski.k%C5%82adzione/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 2 eggs 3 cups flour some oil 2 tbsp salt , 0.25 tsp- 1.2 cups water Cookware small bowl large mixing bowl large pot metal spoon wooden spoon hand strainer colander Steps In a small bowl, beat eggs to mix yolks and white. Place flour in a large mixing bowl, add eggs and salt. Slowly start adding water and beat on low until blended well.</description></item><item><title>Lasagna</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/lasagna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/lasagna/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 2.5 hours; Source: Aunt Julie
Ingredients 1 tsp basil 1 pound ground turkey some minced garlic 0.75 cups onion 1.5 tsp oregano 1 box oven ready lasagna noodles 0.5 cups parmesan 3 tbsp parsley 1 pound petite diced tomatoes 1 tsp salt 2 cups shredded mozzarella 24 ounces small curd cottage cheese 2 tbsp sugar 15 ounces tomato sauce Cookware large bowl 13x9 pan Steps Cook ground turkey, onion and minced garlic.</description></item><item><title>Mac And Cheese</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/mac.and.cheese/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/mac.and.cheese/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 15 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 tbsp butter 2 cups cheddar cheese 2 cups chicken stock 3 cups elbow macaroni 1 tbsp mustard 2 tbsp parmesan 0.12 tsp pepper 0.25 tsp salt 4 ounces velveeta 1 cup water Cookware instant pot Steps Add elbow macaroni, chicken stock, water, butter, parmesan, salt and pepper to the instant pot. [butter: 2 tbsp; chicken stock: 2 cups; elbow macaroni: 3 cups; parmesan: 2 tbsp; pepper: 0.</description></item><item><title>Meat Marinade</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/meat.marinade/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/meat.marinade/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 5 minutes
Ingredients 2 tbsp Italian seasoning 2 tbsp dijon mustard 1 tsp garlic powder 2 tbsp lemon juice 0.33 cups olive oil 1 tbsp pepper 0.25 cups red wine vinegar 1 tbsp salt 1 tbsp sugar 3 tbsp worcestireshire sauce Steps Mix together olive oil, red wine vinegar, worcestireshire sauce, dijon mustard, lemon juice, Italian seasoning, salt, pepper, sugar and garlic powder and slather on meats.</description></item><item><title>Meatloaf</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/meatloaf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/meatloaf/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1 hour; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 envelope dry onion soup mix 2 eggs 1 tsp garlic powder 2 pounds ground beef 0.5 cups pasta sauce 0.67 cups quick oats Cookware oven loaf pan baking sheet Steps Perheat oven to 325 degrees. Mix ground beef, eggs, quick oats, dry onion soup mix, pasta sauce, garlic powder and form into into a loaf shape. [dry onion soup mix: 1 envelope; eggs: 2; garlic powder: 1 tsp; ground beef: 2 pounds; pasta sauce: 0.</description></item><item><title>No Bakes</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/no.bakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/no.bakes/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 30 minutes
Ingredients 4 tbsp butter 0.25 cups cocoa 0.5 cups peanut butter 3 cups quick oats 2 cups sugar 2 tsp vanilla Cookware wax paper Steps Combine sugar, butter, cocoa and bring to a slow boil. [butter: 4 tbsp; cocoa: 0.25 cups; sugar: 2 cups] Turn off heat and add vanilla and peanut butter, then mix well until creamy and smooth before adding quick oats.</description></item><item><title>Pannukakku</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/pannukakku/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/pannukakku/</guid><description>Facts Source: Sumi; Total Time: 30 minutes
Ingredients 3 eggs 0.25 cups flour 1 cup milk 0.25 tsp salt 2 tbsp sugar Cookware 8 inch round cake pans parchment paper Steps Beat eggs until fluffy. [eggs: 3] Add milk, flour, sugar and salt, beating continuously until the mixture has then consistency of thick cream. [flour: 0.25 cups; milk: 1 cup; salt: 0.25 tsp; sugar: 2 tbsp] Pour into 2 8 inch round cake pans lined with parchment paper.</description></item><item><title>Ramen Stir Fry</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ramen.stir.fry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/ramen.stir.fry/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 20 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 8 ounces broccoli florets 1 tbsp brown sugar 1 pound chicken breasts 0.33 cups chicken stock 1 tbsp cornstarch 2 green onions 1 tbsp minced garlic 2 tbsp oil some pepper 1 pack ramen noodles 1 tbsp rice vinegar some salt 1 tbsp sesame seeds 0.25 cups soy sauce some water Cookware small mixing bowl pot wok non-stick pan Steps In a small mixing bowl, whisk together the soy sauce and cornstarch until no lumps remain.</description></item><item><title>Roasted Vegetable</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/roasted.vegetable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/roasted.vegetable/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 30 minutes
Ingredients some asparagus some bell peppers some broccoli some green beans some olive oil some pepper some potatoes some red onion some salt some seasoned salt some sweet potatoes Cookware tin foil baking sheet Steps Cut up whatever vegetables you want to use into bit sized pieces. General recommendations are asparagus, red onion, potatoes, sweet potatoes, bell peppers, broccoli or green beans.</description></item><item><title>Sloppy Joes</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sloppy.joes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sloppy.joes/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 miuntes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 tbsp butter 0.25 tbsp chili powder 1 tbsp garlic 1 pound ground beef 0.25 cups ketchup some mild hot sauce 0.12 cups mustard 0.5 onion 0.5 tsp seasoned salt 0.5 tbsp soy sauce 4 ounces tomato paste 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce Steps Mix worcestershire sauce, soy sauce, chili powder, mustard, ketchup, tomato paste, seasoned salt, mild hot sauce to create a sauce.</description></item><item><title>Slowcooker Mac And Cheese</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/slowcooker.mac.and.cheese/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/slowcooker.mac.and.cheese/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 3 hours; Source: Emma
Ingredients 4 ounces block american cheese 12 ounces block cheddar cheese 0.25 cups butter some cayenne pepper some cold water 0.5 tsp dry mustard 1 pound elbow pasta 12 ounces evaporated milk 0.25 tsp garlic powder 2.5 cups milk non&amp;ndash; some stick spary 0.5 tsp pepper 1 tsp salt Cookware 6-quart slow cooker Steps Spary 6-quart slow cooker with non-stick spary.</description></item><item><title>Spinach Pie</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/spinach.pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/spinach.pie/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 1.5 hours; Source: Matt
Ingredients 1 small jar artichokes 6 tbsp butter 4 ounces cream cheese 1 cup heavy cream 1 tbsp minced garlic 1 onion some pam 0.25 cups parmesan cheese some pepper 2 sheets puff pastry 1 tsp salt 5 ounces spinach Cookware oven 13x9 pan rolling pin large saucepan microwave Steps Preheat oven to 375 degrees. Take out puff pastry and bring it to room temperature, then spray a 13x9 pan with pam.</description></item><item><title>Sweedes</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sweedes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/sweedes/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 45 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 2 cups beef broth 0.5 cups breadcrumbs 1 egg 4 cups egg noodles some garlic 1 pound ground beef 1 cup heavy cream 1 cup milk 0.5 cups minced onion 1 cup parmesan 2 tbsp parsley some pepper some salt 2 tbsp vegetable oil 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce Cookware large bowl large frying pan Steps In a large bowl, combine ground beef, breadcrumbs, minced onion, egg, salt, pepper and garlic.</description></item><item><title>Taco Pie</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/taco.pie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/taco.pie/</guid><description>Facts Source: Matt; Total Time: 1 hour
Ingredients 0.75 cups bisquik 1 cup cheddar cheese some crisco 2 eggs 4 ounces green chiles 1 pound ground beef 1 medium onion 1 cup milk some pam some pepper 1 package taco seasoning Cookware oven 9 inch pie plate bowl Steps Preheat oven to 400 degrees. Grease a 9 inch pie plate with crisco or pam. Cook ground beef and medium onion over medium heat until meat is browned and cooked.</description></item><item><title>Thai Curry Soup</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/thai.curry.soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/thai.curry.soup/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 30 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 0.25 cups basil 2 tbsp brown suger 1.5 pounds chicken 6 cups chicken broth 0.5 cups cilantro 14 ounces coconut milk 1 diced onion 1 tbsp fish sauce 1 tbsp ginger 2 tbsp lime juice 1 tbsp minced garlic 1 tbsp olive oil some pepper 1 red bell pepper 3 tbsp red curry paste 8 ounces rice noodles some salt 3 sliced green onions Cookware large pot Steps Heat olive oil in a large pot over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Tiktok Ramen</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/tiktok.ramen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/tiktok.ramen/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 10 minutes; Source: Emma
Ingredients 1 tbsp brown sugar 1 tbsp butter 1 egg some everything bagel spice some frozen vegetables 1 tbsp minced garlic 1 package ramen noodles 0.25 tsp red pepper flakes 1 tbsp soy sauce Steps Cook the ramen noodles according to package direction and drain well. [ramen noodles: 1 package] In a pan, heat up the butter over medium heat. Stir in the minced garlic and red pepper flakes.</description></item><item><title>Tuna Noodle</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/tuna.noodle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/tuna.noodle/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 45 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients 3 cups bowtie pasta 0.25 cups cheddar cheese 0.25 cups chopped green onion 1 can cream of celery soup 1 tsp seasoned salt 0.5 cups sour cream Cookware casserole dish Steps Cook bowtie pasta according to directions. [bowtie pasta: 3 cups] Combine cream of celery soup, sour cream, seasoned salt, chopped green onion, cheddar cheese and heat until warm and melted.</description></item><item><title>Vegetable Stir Fry</title><link>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/vegetable.stir.fry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mjschwenne.github.io/recipes/recipes/vegetable.stir.fry/</guid><description>Facts Total Time: 45 minutes; Source: Matt
Ingredients some bell pepper some broccoli 2 tbsp brown sugar some carrot 2 tbsp cornstarch some garlic 2 tbsp oil some onion some ramen noodles 2 tbsp sherry some siracha 0.5 cups soy sauce 1 tbsp squeeze ginger Cookware large skillet Steps Perpare whatever vegetables are of interest, normally onion, carrot broccoli and bell pepper. [bell pepper: some; broccoli: some; carrot: some; onion: some] Make a sauce with soy sauce, sherry, brown sugar, cornstarch, siracha, squeeze ginger.</description></item></channel></rss>